prothom-alojobs.com 2008-02-21

# Prothom Alo jobs | Job Site for Best Jobs in Bangladesh | Privacy Policy

| 

|   
---  
|  |   PRIVACY POLICY   
---|---  
|  |   | **Privacy Policy For Jobseekers

* * *

** |    
---|---|---  
  | 

  * **General Inoformation and Disclosure of Information**
  * **User Specific Information**
  * **Resumès and Profiles**
  * **Children**
  * **You Are Responsible**

|    
  |   |    
  | **Privacy Policy For Employers

* * *

** |    
  | 

  * **General Inoformation and Disclosure of Information**
  * **User Specific Information**
  * **Registration Information and Company Profile**
  * **Children**
  * **You Are Responsible**

|    
  |   |    
|   | Privacy Policy For Jobseekers  |    
---|---|---  
  | 

The www.prothom-alojobs.com is at all times interested in providing you with the best possible user experience. Part of our service to you includes a strong commitment to your privacy as our customer. To that end, we endeavor to provide you with a safe, secure service and use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private and is used only for the expressed purposes of www.prothom-alojobs.com. The following statements provide additional details about our privacy commitment. 

|    
---|---|---  
  |  |    
  | **General Information and Disclosure of Information** |    
  |  | 

We gather information about our users collectively, tracking such things as pages visited, number of searches performed, keywords used in searches, etc. We only use this information anonymously and in the aggregate. This information allows us to create a better overall experience for you by gauging the level of traffic, speed, and overall performance of the site. We may share this information with our partners and advertisers to help them better understand our site and services. When we do this, it is only in the aggregate and no information specific to you is released. 

|    
  |  |    
  | **User Specific Information** |    
  |  | 

We offer some services that require that we contact you via email. We will from time to time send you a message from the www.prothom-alojobs.com. These messages may contain information about specific opportunities or announcements about enhancements to our Web site. We do not sell, rent, or lease access to any user's contact information, type of computer, usage patterns, email address, etc. We do not disclose this information unless it is required by law. 

|    
  |  |    
  | **Resumès and Profiles** |    
  |  | 

The www.prothom-alojobs.com is a career and employment Web site. As such, you can store online Resumès on our site to send to employers or to allow employers to search for you. We provide you with several levels of privacy control designed to meet your individual needs. 

You can store your resume in our database and allow potential employers to search for your resume and profile. This means that employers can actively seek you out and contact you when they are interested in your skills. This is the default setting when you create your online resume and profile. 

|    
  |  |    
  | **Children** |    
  |  | 

Our site does not collect information specific to children and does not target children as users. We believe that all children should have the consent of a parent or guardian prior to accessing www.prothom-alojobs.com. Inasmuch as we cannot control a child's access to our site, we encourage parents to utilize Web filtering technology to help you supervise your child's use of this site and the Internet in general. 

|    
  |  |    
  | **You are Responsible** |    
  |  | 

Ultimately; you are responsible for protecting your own privacy online. We endeavor to provide you with the tools necessary to successfully use our service and to protect your privacy. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and your user account information. Please exercise care and caution whenever you are online. 

This privacy statement is for information only, and is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

|    
  | _**^Go to Top^**_ |    
  |   |    
|   | Privacy Policy For Employers  |    
---|---|---  
  | 

The www.prothom-alojobs.com is at all times interested in providing you with the best possible user experience. Part of our service to you includes a strong commitment to your privacy as our customer. To that end, we endeavor to provide you with a safe, secure service and use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private and is used only for the expressed purposes of the Employment Center . The following statements provide additional details about our privacy commitment.

|    
---|---|---  
  |   |    
  | **General Information and Disclosure of Information** |    
  |   | 

We gather information about our users collectively, tracking such things as pages visited, number of searches performed, keywords used in searches, etc. We only use this information anonymously and in the aggregate. This information allows us to create a better overall experience for you by gauging the level of traffic, speed, and overall performance of the site. We may share this information with our partners and advertisers to help them better understand our site and services. When we do this, it is only in the aggregate and no information specific to you is released.

|    
  |   |    
  | **User Specific Information** |    
  |   | 

We offer some services which require that we contact you via email. We will from time to time send you messages from our site. These messages may contain information about specific opportunities or announcements about enhancements to our Web site. We do not sell, rent, or lease access to any users contact information, type of computer, usage patterns, email address, etc. We do not disclose this information unless it is required by law.

|    
  |   |    
  | **Registration Information and Company Profile** |    
  |   | 

The information you provide to us upon registration as a company on the www.prothom-alojobs.com is not released, sold, leased, or otherwise distributed unless such disclosure is required by law. The information you provide in your company profile, however, is intended to be viewed by the general public. Your company profile is meant to be used as a promotional tool to accompany your job advertisements. Information you include in your profile is available to the public via our service.

|    
  |   |    
  | **Children** |    
  |   | 

Our Employment Center does not collect information specific to children and does not target children as users. We believe that all children should have the consent of a parent or guardian prior to accessing the Employment Center . Inasmuch as we cannot control a child's access to our site, we encourage parents to utilize Web filtering technology to help you supervise your child's use of this site and the Internet in general.

|    
  |   |    
  | **You are Responsible** |    
  |   | 

Ultimately, you are responsible for protecting your own privacy online. We endeavor to provide you with the tools necessary to successfully use our service and to protect your privacy. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and your user account information. Please exercise care and caution whenever you are online.

|    
  | _**^Go to Top^**_ |    
  |   |    
  |   |    
  |   |    
  |   |    
  |   |    
  |   |    
  |   |    
  | **This privacy statement is for information only and is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.** |
